ANTONINO LO BIANCO

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER



PROFILE

I'm training to become a web developer with <u>BeCode</u>, and I've also had experience as a marketing manager and graphic designer for Crispin Medical, a medical company, as well as being a sales manager in a boutique at VOO. I'm passionate about web development and my aim is to become a front-end developer with a long-term vision so that I can also master the back-end. With skills such as a desire to learn and commitment, I'm ready to take on stimulating challenges, with a collaborative approach, a critical mind and attention to detail.

CONTACT

Phone: +32(0) 487 30 18 90

Mail: <u>antonino.lobianco@outlook.com</u> Address: <u>Rue des Alcyons 86, 1082 Brussels</u>

LINKS

Portfolio/lbantonino
Linkedin/antoninolobianco
Github/lbantonino

WORK EXPERIENCE

Crispin Médical - Cholet, France

Marketing Director - September 2021 - June 2023

As Marketing Director and Graphic Designer at Crispin Médical, I led specific marketing strategies in the medical sector, merging a graphics business to help the company grow.

VOO - Brussels, Belgium

Sales Manager - September 2019 - July 2021

As Sales Manager at VOO, I perfected the art of boutique selling. My ability to promote and sell products has proved to be a major asset, making a significant contribution to the company's sales performance.

MANPOWER - Brussels, Belgium

Order operator - September 2018 - September 2019

As an order operator at ManPower, I gained effective expertise in order management. My contribution has boosted the company's operational efficiency.

EDUCATION

BeCode - Web Development

BeCode (Brussels) - August 2023 - March 2024

Bachelor's degree in advertising

ESA Saint-Luc Brussels - September 2015 - June 2018

CESS computer graphics

Saint-Luc Institute Brussels - June 2015

LANGUAGES

French (native language) English (B1) Dutch (B1)

SKILLS

MERN Full-Stack Front-end specialist, REACT Problem solving Task-oriented objective